### **CAREER PROFILE**

I am an experienced leader who has worked with different foundations in both the customer service and operational sides of business. I am very interested in using the skills I've already obtained to further my career in the business world.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Head Cashier**

February 2017 - Present

Lowe's Home Improvement, Rochester, MI

I was hired by Lowe's as a seasonal employee in the flooring department In just a few months I was offered a promotion into a full time management role. In my current role I'm responsible for ensuring that money is distributed and pulled from the registers before opening, after closing, and when registers have reached a certain cash limit. On a daily basis I was also accountable for ensuring the cashiers are operating effectively, reducing shrink, and providing the necessary training to give each employee the skills to succeed.

#### Assistant Branch Manager

July 2017 - February 2018

TCF Bank, Rochester, Mi.

As the assistant branch manager it was my job to ensure the branch was compliant with all of the necessary audits, From ensuring that cash and negotiable instruments are correctly processed with the federal reserve, to ensuring that documents are retained for the correct amount of time. On a day to day basis I would also set up meetings with potential and current clients to build and maintain long relationships with personal clients and business customers in the surrounding area.

I have created and implemented outside sales plans and guides that were used in our yearly round table meetings and distributed to all Michigan branches to help further push business relationships.

In this roll I also took it upon myself to immerse myself in the leadership roll and develop new training guides for my staff. Each employee was given a binder where training material was kept. I would hold monthly meetings with each employee to ensure they felt like they were on the right track in their career development and take time ensure I understood what their goals were and the best way to help them obtain them.

# Bartender

September 2016 - July 2017

Desert Rose Casino, Alturas, CA

As a bartender for the Desert Rose Casino I was required to act quickly and accurately while serving drinks as well as making monetary transactions. Beyond serving the customers safety was a top priority, ensuring customers were not over served and are safe was my main responsibility, being able to think promptly and calmly needed to be escalated and when security needed to be called.

## Operational Branch Services Officer

WestAmerica Bank, Healdsburg, CA

March 2016 - September 2016

At WestAmerica Bank I was responsible from all things operational from account openings to audits. Building customer and community relationships was key in this role. I was in charge of organizing the banks float in the annual summer parade for the town of Healdsburg. This meant going beyond my daily work tasks to complete unique tasks that were assigned to me. Using resources in and around the community, our float placed third in the parade. This job more than others taught me the importance of organization. Being organized made sticking to the time line possible which completed the task.

# **Branch Supervisor**

January 2014 - February 2016

Tcf Bank, Rochester. MI

I started at Tcf Bank as a Teller II which I was able to demonstrate my eagerness to learn and my attention to detail. I was quickly beyond the teller line, learning to open accounts and learning operations. I was promoted to teller III and then to branch supervisor. As a branch Supervisor my main responsibility was to assist the tellers and ensure the teller line is running as smoothly as possible We could open and close accounts if the branch manager and assistant branch manager were unavailable.

# Sales Associate

May 2011 - December 2013

The Home Depot, Sugar land, TX.

As a sales associate at The Home Depot I was responsible for assisting customers while maintaining a neat and organized department. Ensuring that freight is brought to the floor and worked onto the shelves in a timely fashion for customers. If a customer is looking for a product that is unavailable at the store, trying to see if it's something we could special order for the customer. This job was really the foundation for my customer service experience.



# Tylor Faccini

Client Care Specialis

**4** 248.520.6055

ylorfaccini.github.io

#### **SKILLS**

Able to handle high stress situations and complete tasks on a deadline.

Ability to from excellent customer and co worker relationships.

Proficient with technology.

Proven ability to grow and be promoted within companies.

#### **TECHNOLOGY**

Windows

MacOS

Microsoft Office

VOIP phone systems

HTML

# REFERENCES

Michael Andrejewski 586-943-1856

Lowe's Home Improvement Service Manager

Matthew Tallant 248-761-0737 TCF Bank Branch Manager

Debi Renyolds 530-233-3141 Desert Rose Casino HR Manager

## **EDUCATION**

High School Diploma George Bush High School May 2011